<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<resources>
    <template>
        <question>
            <text>how do i access my benefits</text>
            <text>my benefits</text>
            <text>benefits</text>
            <text>where can i find information on benefits</text>
        </question>
        <response>Access this information through the CGI portal Select Tools local tools and then Member Flexible Benefits This page given you information and links to the Member flexible benefits pages Where you can choose the benefits that best suit your life for the next year
        </response>
    </template>
    <template>
        <question>
            <text>how do i write my cv</text>
            <text>cv templates</text>
            <text>cv</text>
        </question>
        <response>First go to the CGI portal Click on Tools and then the templates link Click the Cv's and biography link and download them When that's completed upload to your EPMS profile
        </response>
    </template>
    <template>
        <question>
            <text>timesheet</text>
            <text>timesheets</text>
        </question>
        <response>Timesheets are best to go through with your buddy so that they can make sure your doing things correctly until your used to it You can find those through the CGI portal, click *MY CGI* and then click the _timesheets_ link sign in with your usual sign in details and you'll be redirected to the page Just remember to get your timesheet submitted by midday *Friday* or directors burst into tears! :grinning:
        </response>
    </template>
    <template>
        <question>
            <text>courses</text>
            <text>skillsport</text>
            <text>plurasight</text>
        </question>
        <response>For accessing courses and providers like skillsport Again open your web browser and navigate to the CGI portal Click the Tools tab then click the Learning tools link This will redirect you to the learning landing page
        </response>
    </template>
    <template>
        <question>
            <text>cgi profile</text>
        </question>
        <response>To find your CGI profile just do the following Navigate to the CGI portal page and go through the login steps Under the Banner heading you'll see a few tabs, click the profile tab.
        </response>
    </template>
    <template>
        <question>
            <text>hr portal</text>
            <text>hr case</text>
            <text>hr</text>
        </question>
        <response>You'll need to go to the HR service desk Navigate to the CGI portal and mouse over the tools link Select the HR service center under the Member support link This will open a new tab where you can deal with HR and payroll and expenses issues
        </response>
    </template>
    <template>
        <question>
            <text>book travel</text>
            <text>travel</text>
            <text>hotel</text>
        </question>
        <response>Navigate to the CGI portal and select Tools Go to Local Tools and then select the CGI Travel Portal link From there you can book travel and see any restrictions that you have to meet before booking
        </response>
    </template>
    <template>
        <question>
            <text>global pay</text>
            <text>pay issues</text>
            <text>pay statement</text>
            <text>pay</text>
        </question>
        <response>Use the CGI portal and follow these steps Select Tools Local tools GlobalView Pay This will take you directly to the myView page, you'll find a view mypay button Click that to see your pay breakdown and access your pay statement
        </response>
    </template>
    <template>
        <question>
            <text>applications hub</text>
        </question>
        <response>Access the applications hub through the CGI portal Select Tools Local Tools and click on Applications Hub
        </response>
    </template>
    <template>
        <question>
            <text>search</text>
        </question>
        <response>That's a very broad subject For that information I'd recommend you access the CGI portal And use the search feature in the top right hand section of the page.
        </response>
    </template>
    <template>
        <question>
            <text>it issues</text>
            <text>it help desk</text>
            <text>it service desk</text>
        </question>
        <response>You can raise an IT issue through their service desk Navigate to the CGI portal and then select Tools Memeber Support IT Service Portal.
        </response>
    </template>
    <template>
        <question>
            <text>expenses</text>
        </question>
        <response>This is in the same place as the timesheets Use the CGI portal, Tools then Local Tools and then Timesheets and expenses.
        </response>
    </template>
    <template>
        <question>
            <text>book meeting room</text>
            <text>meeting room</text>
            <text>book a meeting room</text>
            <text>booking meeting rooms</text>
        </question>
        <response>This is different depending on where you are located The best advice I can give you here is to use the CGI portal, in the top right You'll find the search box try searching there for your location followed by room booking
        </response>
    </template>
</resources>
